{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","address":"9137 W Grand River Ave","zipcode":"48204","owner":"Falcon Holdings, LLC","licenseNumber":"035229","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":null,"establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E610000094AACE195AC854C0F0A47556B62E4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44866","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","inspectionDate":"2019-01-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"45034","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","inspectionDate":"2019-01-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"45034","inspectionDate":"1/14/2019","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"45034","inspectionDate":"1/14/2019","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"holes or gaps along floors","problemDescription":"Not tight-fitting","subProblem":"","location":"OUTER DOOR(S)","subLocation":"At the Back door","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements above."},{"inspectionid":"45034","inspectionDate":"1/14/2019","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Harborage conditions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not eliminated","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Eliminate harborage conditions."},{"inspectionid":"45034","inspectionDate":"1/14/2019","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"43267","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","inspectionDate":"2018-07-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"3","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43267","inspectionDate":"7/3/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cooler (undercounter)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"43267","inspectionDate":"7/3/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cooler (undercounter)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"43267","inspectionDate":"7/3/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the Water lines","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"43267","inspectionDate":"7/3/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"ceiling(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"CEILING","subLocation":"Throughout Facility","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"43267","inspectionDate":"7/3/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"and the front","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"inspectionid":"43267","inspectionDate":"7/3/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"4-502.11","violationDescription":"(A) UTENSILS shall be maintained in a state of repair or condition that complies with the requirements specified under Parts 4-1 and 4-2 or shall be discarded.\r\n(B) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be calibrated in accordance with manufacturer's specifications as necessary to ensure their accuracy. (Pf)   \r\n(C) Ambient air temperature, water pressure, and water TEMPERATURE MEAURING DEVICES shall be maintained in good repair and be accurate within the intended range of use.","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"For the Utensil storage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"43204","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","inspectionDate":"2018-06-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43204","inspectionDate":"6/15/2018","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"rodents mice","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."}]},{"inspectionid":"40562","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","inspectionDate":"2017-10-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"2","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40562","inspectionDate":"10/24/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"40562","inspectionDate":"10/24/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"3-501.19","violationDescription":"If time only, rather than time in conjunction with temperature, is used as the public health control for a working supply of POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  before cooking, or for READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  that is displayed or held for service for immediate consumption:   \r\n(1)   Written procedures are required to be prepared in advance, maintained in the establishment, and made available to the REGULATORY AUTHORITY upon request.(Pf)\r\n(2)   The FOOD shall be marked to indicate the time that is 4 hrs past the point in which food is removed from temperature control, or 6 hrs if the temperature is maintained below 70°F. (Pf)\r\n(3)   Food in unmarked containers or in containers that exceed the time limit are to be discarded. (P)\r\n        \r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Time controlled food(s)","subItem":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","problemDescription":"Held past time control mark","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Steam table","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"40562","inspectionDate":"10/24/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Failed to notify the health department that an employee is diagnosed with a \"big 4\" illness","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Front counter","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Notify as required by code."},{"inspectionid":"40562","inspectionDate":"10/24/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\r\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\r\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\r\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\r\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\r\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\r\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\r\n\r\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Quaternary ammonia solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 100 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE WINDOW","subLocation":"At the Front counter","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"inspectionid":"40562","inspectionDate":"10/24/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"gnats","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"In the Back Room","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."}]},{"inspectionid":"38652","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","inspectionDate":"2017-05-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"127","pcount":"1","pfcount":"5","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"6","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"5","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38652","inspectionDate":"5/9/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"2-301.15","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands in a HANDWASHING SINK or APPROVED automatic handwashing facility and may not clean their hands in a sink used for FOOD preparation or WAREWASHING, or in a service sink or a curbed cleaning facility used for the disposal of mop water and similar liquid waste. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Employee washed/rinsed hands","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In three compartment sink","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed in handsink(s) only."},{"inspectionid":"38652","inspectionDate":"5/9/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\r\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\r\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\r\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\r\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\r\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\r\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\r\n\r\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Quaternary ammonia solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 100 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"inspectionid":"38652","inspectionDate":"5/9/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"38652","inspectionDate":"5/9/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at restroom handsink","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"38652","inspectionDate":"5/9/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"38652","inspectionDate":"5/9/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-302.11","violationDescription":"A supply of toilet tissue shall be available at each toilet.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Toilet paper","subItem":"at toilet in restroom men's","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"36850","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","inspectionDate":"2016-10-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"3","pfcount":"2","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"5","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"5","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36850","inspectionDate":"10/5/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cooler (undercounter)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"36850","inspectionDate":"10/5/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"36850","inspectionDate":"10/5/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Adulterated/contaminated","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cooler (top loader)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"36850","inspectionDate":"10/5/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"36850","inspectionDate":"10/5/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"MFL289.4119","violationDescription":"Sec. 4119. (1) Except as otherwise provided in subsection (2), a person licensed as a food establishment under this chapter shall keep a copy of the current license or temporary license furnished by the department posted and exposed in a conspicuous place for public inspection. A conspicuous place is the principal place where food business is transacted.  (2) In the case of vending machines, the name and address and telephone number of the current vending machine location operator shall be conspicuously displayed on each vending machine.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food Service License","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not displayed","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36850","inspectionDate":"10/5/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"36850","inspectionDate":"10/5/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-302.11","violationDescription":"A supply of toilet tissue shall be available at each toilet.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Toilet paper","subItem":"at toilet in restroom women's","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"36850","inspectionDate":"10/5/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1146","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #855","violationCode":"6-501.112","violationDescription":"Dead or trapped birds, insects, rodents, and other pests shall be removed from control devices and the PREMISES at a frequency that prevents their accumulation,  decomposition, or the attraction of pests.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Dead/trapped pest(s)","subItem":"flies","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1146"}}